HERE Organizing Department Files on Microfilm 6199/003 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- W.R.O. Org. Files Cartridge no. 5-A (Reel 46)
  - Western Regional Office Organizer Files, 1974-1980; 9 (Reel 46)
    Stafford, J.
  - Western Regional Office Organizer Files, 1974-1980; 10 (Reel 46)
    Tobin, J.
  - Western Regional Office Organizer Files, 1974-1980; 11 (Reel 46)
    Vuchinich, L.
  - Western Regional Office Organizer Files, 1974-1980; 12 (Reel 46)
    Walsh, J.
  - Western Regional Office Organizer Files, 1974-1980; 13 (Reel 46)
    Local Special Organizer
  - Western Regional Office Organizer Files, 1974-1980; 14 (Reel 46)
    Local 49
  - Western Regional Office Organizer Files, 1974-1980; 15 (Reel 46)
    Local 470
  - Western Regional Office Organizer Files, 1974-1980; 16 (Reel 46)
    Local 715
- E.R.O. Org. Files Reel 6-A (Reel 47)
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 1 (Reel 47)
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 2 (Reel 47)
    International Affairs
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 3 (Reel 47)
    Belfoure, M.
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 4 (Reel 47)
    Bick, D.
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 5 (Reel 47)
    Burger, H.
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 6 (Reel 47)
    Cortez, J.
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 7 (Reel 47)
    Davis, E.
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 8 (Reel 47)
    Drapkin, M.
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 9 (Reel 47)
    Duffy, S.
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 10 (Reel 47)
    Ellenbarger, N.
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 11 (Reel 47)
    Feder, L.
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 12 (Reel 47)
    Fernandez, A.
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 13 (Reel 47)
    Gonzalez, A.
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 14 (Reel 47)
    Green, T.
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 15 (Reel 47)
    Gorgan, P.
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 16 (Reel 47)
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 17 (Reel 47)
    Kelly, B.
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 18 (Reel 47)
    Kistler, K.
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 19 (Reel 47)
    Konstantelos
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 20 (Reel 47)
    McCarney, A.
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 21 (Reel 47)
    McCarthy, J.
- E.R.O. Files - General and State & Local cartridge no. 1-ERO (Reel 48)
  - Eastern Regional Office General Files, 1979; 1 (Reel 48)
    A
  - Eastern Regional Office General Files, 1979; 2 (Reel 48)
    AFL-CIO
  - Eastern Regional Office - General Files, 1979; 3 (Reel 48)
    Ara Services, Inc.
  - Eastern Regional Office - General Files, 1979; 4 (Reel 48)
    A. Phillip Randolph Institute
  - Eastern Regional Office - General Files, 1979; 5 (Reel 48)
    Alyeska
  - Eastern Regional Office - General Files, 1979; 6 (Reel 48)
    Article XX
  - Eastern Regional Office - General Files, 1979; 7 (Reel 48)
    Brown Reception
  - Eastern Regional Office - General Files, 1979; 8 (Reel 48)
    Campaigns
  - Eastern Regional Office - General Files, 1979; 9 (Reel 48)
    Contract Research
  - Eastern Regional Office - General Files, 1979; 10 (Reel 48)
    Cope
  - Eastern Regional Office - General Files, 1979; 11 (Reel 48)
    Crown Center
  - Eastern Regional Office - General Files, 1979; 12 (Reel 48)
    Enckell, Larry
  - Eastern Regional Office - General Files, 1979; 13 (Reel 48)
    General Correspondence to Organizers
  - Eastern Regional Office - General Files, 1979; 14 (Reel 48)
    Geneva ILO Convention 1974
  - Eastern Regional Office - General Files, 1979; 15 (Reel 48)
    Gibson-GST Correspondence
  - Eastern Regional Office - General Files, 1979; 16 (Reel 48)
    Hanley-GP Correspondence
  - Eastern Regional Office - General Files, 1979; 17 (Reel 48)
    Holiday Inn, Bethesda, #75
  - Eastern Regional Office - General Files, 1979; 18 (Reel 48)
    International Unions
  - Eastern Regional Office - General Files, 1979; 19 (Reel 48)
    IUF
  - Eastern Regional Office - General Files, 1979; 20 (Reel 48)
    Kennedy Center
  - Eastern Regional Office - General Files, 1979; 21 (Reel 48)
    Miscellaneous
  - Eastern Regional Office - General Files, 1979; 22 (Reel 48)
    NLRB
  - Eastern Regional Office - General Files, 1979; 23 (Reel 48)
    Ohio Inns, Inc.
  - Eastern Regional Office - General Files, 1979; 24 (Reel 48)
    Originals
  - Eastern Regional Office - General Files, 1979; 25 (Reel 48)
    Paulsen-Do Correspondence
  - Eastern Regional Office - General Files, 1979; 26 (Reel 48)
    Prepaid Legal
  - Eastern Regional Office - General Files, 1979; 27 (Reel 48)
    S
  - Eastern Regional Office - General Files, 1979; 28 (Reel 48)
    Sheraton
  - Eastern Regional Office - General Files, 1979; 29 (Reel 48)
    Sheraton-Lanham, MD.
  - Eastern Regional Office - General Files, 1979; 30 (Reel 48)
    Stouffer
  - Eastern Regional Office - General Files, 1979; 31 (Reel 48)
    Stouffers-Atlanta
  - Eastern Regional Office - General Files, 1979; 32 (Reel 48)
    Tulsa, OK - Hilton
  - Eastern Regional Office - General Files, 1979; 33 (Reel 48)
    Williamsburg, VA
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 34 (Reel 48)
    Alabama
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 35 (Reel 48)
    Mobile, AL
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 36 (Reel 48)
    Birmingham, AL
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 37 (Reel 48)
    Arkansas
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 38 (Reel 48)
    California
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 39 (Reel 48)
    Colorado
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 40 (Reel 48)
    Connecticut
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 41 (Reel 48)
    Connecticut Conference
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 42 (Reel 48)
    District of Columbia
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 43 (Reel 48)
    D.C. - Washington Joint Board
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 44 (Reel 48)
    D.C. - #25
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 45 (Reel 48)
    D.C. - #75
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 46 (Reel 48)
    D.C. - Sheraton Contract
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 47 (Reel 48)
    D.C. - #781
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 48 (Reel 48)
    Florida
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 49 (Reel 48)
    Florida - #104
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 50 (Reel 48)
    Florida - #355
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 51 (Reel 48)
    Florida - #737
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 52 (Reel 48)
    Georgia
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 53 (Reel 48)
    Georgia - Atlanta
- E.R.O. Org. Files State & Local reel 2-ERO (Reel 49)
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 1 (Reel 49)
    Georgia - Atlanta (cont.)
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 2 (Reel 49)
    Georgia - #190, Savannah
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 3 (Reel 49)
    Idaho
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 4 (Reel 49)
    Illinois
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 5 (Reel 49)
    Iowa
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 6 (Reel 49)
    Kansas
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 7 (Reel 49)
    Kentucky
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 8 (Reel 49)
    Louisiana
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 9 (Reel 49)
    Massachusetts
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 10 (Reel 49)
    Maryland
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 11 (Reel 49)
    Maryland - #36
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 12 (Reel 49)
    Maryland - Baltimore Hilton
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 13 (Reel 49)
    Maryland - Martin's West
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 14 (Reel 49)
    Maryland - Playboy Club
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 15 (Reel 49)
    Michigan
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 16 (Reel 49)
    Michigan - #24
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 17 (Reel 49)
    Mississippi
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 18 (Reel 49)
    Missouri
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 19 (Reel 49)
    Montana
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 20 (Reel 49)
    Nevada
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 21 (Reel 49)
    New Jersey
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 22 (Reel 49)
    New Mexico
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 23 (Reel 49)
    New York
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 24 (Reel 49)
    North Carolina
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 25 (Reel 49)
    Ohio
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 26 (Reel 49)
    Ohio - Ohio Inns
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 27 (Reel 49)
    Ohio - Stouffers
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 28 (Reel 49)
    Oklahoma
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 29 (Reel 49)
    Oregon
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 30 (Reel 49)
    Pennsylvania
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 31 (Reel 49)
    Puerto Rico
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 32 (Reel 49)
    Puerto Rico - #610
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 33 (Reel 49)
    South Carolina
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 34 (Reel 49)
    South Carolina - Myrtle Beach
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 35 (Reel 49)
    Tennessee
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 36 (Reel 49)
    Tennessee - #775
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 37 (Reel 49)
    Tennessee - #847
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 38 (Reel 49)
    Tennessee - Holiday Inn
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 39 (Reel 49)
    Tennessee - Medicenter
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 40 (Reel 49)
    Tennessee - Quality Inn
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 41 (Reel 49)
    Tennessee - St. Judes Hospital
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 42 (Reel 49)
    Texas
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 43 (Reel 49)
    Utah
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 44 (Reel 49)
    Virginia
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 45 (Reel 49)
    Virginia - #23
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 46 (Reel 49)
    Virginia - #121
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 47 (Reel 49)
    Washington
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 48 (Reel 49)
    West Virginia
  - Eastern Regional Office - State and Local Files, 1979; 49 (Reel 49)
    Wisconsin
- E.R.O. Org. Files cartridge no. 7-A (Reel 50)
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 1 (Reel 50)
    McCollum, C.
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 2 (Reel 50)
    McDonnell, C.
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 3 (Reel 50)
    McVey, M.
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 4 (Reel 50)
    Miralles, J.
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 5 (Reel 50)
    O'Brien, F.
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 6 (Reel 50)
    Oppenheim, H.
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 7 (Reel 50)
    Potts, E.
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 8 (Reel 50)
    Race, M.
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 9 (Reel 50)
    Ratkovich, J.
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 10 (Reel 50)
    Reid, L.
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 11 (Reel 50)
    Richardson, D.
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 12 (Reel 50)
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 13 (Reel 50)
    Richardson, H.
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 14 (Reel 50)
    Roberts, W.
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 15 (Reel 50)
    Schiffman, H.
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 16 (Reel 50)
    Skolnik, R.
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 17 (Reel 50)
    Timperio, J.
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 18 (Reel 50)
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 19 (Reel 50)
    Vazques, A.
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 20 (Reel 50)
    Wells, P.
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 21 (Reel 50)
    Local Special Organizer, Local 36
- ERO. Org. & Chron. Files cartridge no. 8-A (Reel 51)
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 1 (Reel 51)
    Local Special Organizer, Local 23
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 2 (Reel 51)
    Local Special Organizer, Local 166
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 3 (Reel 51)
    Local Special Organizer, Local 190
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 4 (Reel 51)
    Local Special Organizer, Local 335
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 5 (Reel 51)
    Local Special Organizer, Local 652
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 6 (Reel 51)
    Local Special Organizer, Local 886
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 7 (Reel 51)
    Check Off List
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 8 (Reel 51)
    Reports Sent to Schiffman, H.
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 9 (Reel 51)
    Delinquent Forms
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1975; 10 (Reel 51)
    Kircher - January 1975
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1975; 11 (Reel 51)
    Kircher - February 1975
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1975; 12 (Reel 51)
    Kircher - March 1975
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1975; 13 (Reel 51)
    Kircher - April 1975
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1975; 14 (Reel 51)
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1975; 15 (Reel 51)
    Pending File
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1973-1974; 16 (Reel 51)
    W.L.K. File - December 1973-March 1974
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1974; 17 (Reel 51)
    W.L.K. File - April-July 1974
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1974; 18 (Reel 51)
    W.L.K. File - August 1974
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1974; 19 (Reel 51)
    W.L.K. File - September 1974
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1974; 20 (Reel 51)
    W.L.K. File - October 1974
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1974; 21 (Reel 51)
    W.L.K. File - November 1974
  - Eastern Regional Office Organizer Files, 1974; 22 (Reel 51)
    W.L.K. File - December 1974
- Misc. Hotel & Restaurant Employees reel 14-A (Reel 52)
  - LSO Weekly Reports Local 1, 1985; 1 (Reel 52)
  - LSO Weekly Reports Local 7, 1985; 2 (Reel 52)
  - LSO Weekly Reports Local 8, 1985; 3 (Reel 52)
  - LSO Weekly Reports Local 10, 1985; 4 (Reel 52)
  - LSO Weekly Reports Local 15, 1985; 5 (Reel 52)
  - LSO Weekly Reports Local 16, 1985; 6 (Reel 52)
  - LSO Weekly Reports Local 23, 1985; 7 (Reel 52)
  - LSO Weekly Reports Local 25, 1985; 8 (Reel 52)
  - LSO Weekly Reports Local 26, 1985; 9 (Reel 52)
  - LSO Weekly Reports Local 30, 1985; 10 (Reel 52)
  - LSO Weekly Reports Local 40, 1985; 11 (Reel 52)
  - LSO Weekly Reports Local 51, 1985; 12 (Reel 52)
  - LSO Weekly Reports Local 70, 1985; 13 (Reel 52)
  - LSO Weekly Reports Local 84, 1985; 14 (Reel 52)
  - LSO Weekly Reports Local 88, 1985; 15 (Reel 52)
  - LSO Weekly Reports Local 99, 1985; 16 (Reel 52)
  - LSO Weekly Reports Local 100, 1985; 17 (Reel 52)
  - LSO Weekly Reports Local 122, 1985; 18 (Reel 52)
  - LSO Weekly Reports Local 165, 1985; 19 (Reel 52)
  - LSO Weekly Reports Local 206, 1985; 20 (Reel 52)
  - LSO Weekly Reports Local 261, 1985; 21 (Reel 52)
- LSO Financial Assistance - 1985 Additions - 1986 Local 40 Van Couver, Canada roll #16A Master (Reel 53)
  - Local 4 - Buffalo, NY - Money Letters, 1985; 1 (Reel 53)
  - Local 17 - Minneapolis, MN - Organizing Subsidy - Proposition #839, 1985; 2 (Reel 53)
  - Financial Assistance Files, 1986; 3 (Reel 53)
  - Local 1 - Chicago, IL - LSO Reports, 4 (Reel 53)
  - Local 4 - Buffalo, NY - Organizing Subsidy, 5 (Reel 53)
  - Local 8 - Seattle, WA - Trudy Springer, 6 (Reel 53)
  - Local 15 - Alton, IL - LSO Reports, 1986; 7 (Reel 53)
  - Local 15 - Southern Illinois Holiday Inn Strike, 1986; 8 (Reel 53)
  - Local 16 - Central Illinois Holiday Inn Peoria, IL - Proposition #1459, 9 (Reel 53)
  - Local 16 - Central Illinois - LSO Reports, 1986; 10 (Reel 53)
  - Local 17 - Minneapolis, MN - Organizing Subsidy, 1986; 11 (Reel 53)
  - Local 30 - San Diego, CA - LSO Reports, 1986; 12 (Reel 53)
  - Local 40 - Vancouver, BC, Canada - LSO Reports, 1986; 13 (Reel 53)
  - Local 40 - Vancouver, BC, Canada - Fraser Valley Veterian Lockout, 1986; 14 (Reel 53)
- LSO Financial Assistance -- Local 50 Hayward, CA - 1986 Local 767 LSO Reports roll #17A Master (Reel 54)
  - Local 50 - Hayward, CA - LSO Reports, 1986; 1 (Reel 54)
  - Local 51 - Traverse City, MI - LSO Reports, 1986; 2 (Reel 54)
  - Local 66 - Merged to Form Local #4 (3/1/87), 1987; 3 (Reel 54)
  - Local 70 - Indianapolis, IN - LSO Reports, 1986; 4 (Reel 54)
  - Local 84 - LSO Reports #946A (12/30/85 - 6/28/86), 1985-1986; 5 (Reel 54)
  - Local 88 - Toronto, Ontario, Canada - LSO Reports, 1986; 6 (Reel 54)
  - Local 99 - Duluth, MN - LSO Reports, 1985-1986; 7 (Reel 54)
  - Local 100 - New York, NY - LSO Reports, 1986; 8 (Reel 54)
  - Local 122 - Milwaukee, WI - LSO Reports, 1986; 9 (Reel 54)
  - Local 165 - Las Vegas, NV - LSO Reports, 1986; 10 (Reel 54)
  - Local 206 - Winnipeg, Man., Canada - LSO Reports, 1985-1986; 11 (Reel 54)
  - Local 450 - Forest Park, IL - LSO Reports, 1986; 12 (Reel 54)
  - Local 471 - LSO Reports, 1986; 13 (Reel 54)
  - Local 540 - International Falls, MN - Financial Assistance, 14 (Reel 54)
  - Local 767 - Regina Sask. Canada - LSO Reports, 1986; 15 (Reel 54)
- LSO Financial Assistance - 1987 LSO Financial Asst. - Local 54 Atlantic City Hotel Strike #2 roll #18A Master (Reel 55)
  - LSO Financial Assistance, 1987; 1 (Reel 55)
  - Local 1 - Chicago, IL, 1987; 2 (Reel 55)
  - Formerly Local 66 - Organizing Subsidy, 1987; 3 (Reel 55)
  - Local 15 - Southern IL - Holiday Inn Strike, 4 (Reel 55)
  - Local 15 - Southern IL - Holiday Inn Marion Illinois, 5 (Reel 55)
  - Local 15 - Southern IL - LSO, 1987; 6 (Reel 55)
  - Local 16 - Central Illinois - Money Subsidies, 7 (Reel 55)
  - Local 17 - Minneapolis, MN - Organizing Subsidy, 1987; 8 (Reel 55)
  - Local 17 - Organizing Subsidy #1673, 1989; 9 (Reel 55)
  - Local 30 - San Diego, CA - David Arizmendia, 10 (Reel 55)
  - Local 40 - Vancouver, BC, Canada - Lockout Royal Canadian Legion #26, 11 (Reel 55)
  - Local 40 - Strike Fraser Valley Veteran Lockout, 12 (Reel 55)
  - Local 40 - Vancouver, BC - LSO, 1987; 13 (Reel 55)
  - Local 54 - Atlantic City, NJ - Atlantis Strike, 1987; 14 (Reel 55)
  - Local 54 - Atlantic City, NJ - Atlantis Hotel Strike #2, 15 (Reel 55)
- LSO Financial Assistance - Exp. Incurred Organizing Medow Lands Sheradon - Local 206 Winnipeg Man. Canada LSO Reports roll #19A Master (Reel 56)
  - Expenses Incurred While Organizing the Meadow Lands Sheradon Hotel, 1 (Reel 56)
  - Local 70 - Indianapolis, IN, 1987; 2 (Reel 56)
  - Local 84 - Toledo, OH - Morg. Johnson, 1987; 3 (Reel 56)
  - Local 84 - Toledo, OH - In Toll Road Marriott Decertification, 4 (Reel 56)
  - Local 86 - Reno, NV - Organizing Subsidy, 5 (Reel 56)
  - Local 99 - Duluth, MN - Propositions #1395, 1395A, 1395B, 1395C, 1987; 6 (Reel 56)
  - Local 99 Duluth, MN - Hacienda Sol Strike, 1987; 7 (Reel 56)
  - 1987 Continuation, 8 (Reel 56)
  - Local 100 - LSO File, 1987; 9 (Reel 56)
  - Local 122, 1987; 10 (Reel 56)
  - Local 165 - Las Vegas, NV, 11 (Reel 56)
  - Local 206 - Winnipeg, Man., Canada - LSO Reports, 12 (Reel 56)
- LSO Financial Assistance - 1987 Local 217 New Haven - Local 21 Rochester, N.J. LSO Subsidy roll #20A Master (Reel 57)
  - Local 217 - New Haven, CT - Organizing Subsidy, 1987; 1 (Reel 57)
  - Local 217 - New Haven, CT - Sheraton Strike, 2 (Reel 57)
  - Local 301 - Philadelphia, PA - Organizing, 1987; 3 (Reel 57)
  - Local 312 - Kalispell, Montana - Local Special Organizer Subsidy Proposition #1861, 4 (Reel 57)
  - Local 427 - Missoula, MT - LSO Proposition #1599A, 5 (Reel 57)
  - Local 450 - Forest Park, IL - LSO, 1987; 6 (Reel 57)
  - Local 471 - Albany, NY - Proposition #871B, 1987; 7 (Reel 57)
  - Local 483 - Monterey, CA - Organizing Subsidy, 1987; 8 (Reel 57)
  - Local 662 - Halifax, N.S., Canada - LSO, 1987; 9 (Reel 57)
  - Local 767 - Regina, Saskatchewan - LSO, 1987; 10 (Reel 57)
  - 1988 Financial Assistance Files, 11 (Reel 57)
  - Local 1 LSO, 1988; 12 (Reel 57)
  - Local 4 - Buffalo, NY - Organizing Subsidy Proposition #1294B, 1988-1989; 13 (Reel 57)
  - Local 5 - Hawaii Strike Kaluakoi, 14 (Reel 57)
  - Local 7 - Baltimore, MD - LSO, 15 (Reel 57)
  - Local 10 - Cleveland, OH, 16 (Reel 57)
  - Local 12 - Cincinnati, OH - Fernald Atomic Plant Strike, 1988; 17 (Reel 57)
  - Local 15 - Alton, IL - LSO, 1988; 18 (Reel 57)
  - Local 17 - Minneapolis, MN - Organizing Subsidy 1988, 19 (Reel 57)
  - Local 17 - Minneapolis, MN - Proposition #2998 - Nakins Restaurant Strike, 20 (Reel 57)
  - Local 21 - Rochester, NY - LSO Subsidy, 21 (Reel 57)
- LSO Financial Assistance - Local 25 Washington D.C. - Local 51, Traverse City Mich., LSO Subsidy roll #21A Master (Reel 58)
  - Local 25 - Washington, D.C. - Organizing Subsidy, 1 (Reel 58)
  - Local 26 - Boston, MA - LSO, 1988; 2 (Reel 58)
  - Local 28 - Oakland, CA - LSO Proposition #2216, 3 (Reel 58)
  - Local 30 - San Diego, CA - Proposition #1207-B, 1988; 4 (Reel 58)
  - Local 40 - 1988 LSO, 5 (Reel 58)
  - Local 40 - Vancouver, B.C., Canada - Royal Canadian Legion #26 Strike, 6 (Reel 58)
  - Local 50 - Hayward Two LSO, 7 (Reel 58)
  - Local 49 - Sacramento, CA - Picket Expenses, 1988; 8 (Reel 58)
  - Local 51 - Traverse City, MI - LSO Subsidy, 9 (Reel 58)
- LSO Financial Assistance - 1988 Local 54 Atlantic City, N.J. Strike Bene. - Local 100 New York, N.Y. LSO Subsidy Roll #22A Master (Reel 59)
  - Local 54 - Atlantic City, NJ - 1988 Strike Benefits at Atlantis Hotel, 1 (Reel 59)
  - Local 57- Pittsburgh, PA - LSO, 2 (Reel 59)
  - Local 62 - Fresno, CA - Local Special Organizer, 3 (Reel 59)
  - Local 64 - Kansas City, MO, 4 (Reel 59)
  - Local 70 - Columbus/Dayton/Indiana - LSO Subsidy, 5 (Reel 59)
  - Local 70 - Dayton, OH - Sheraton Airport Inn Lockout, 6 (Reel 59)
  - Local 75 - Toronto, Ontario, Canada - Proposition #2389, 7 (Reel 59)
  - Local 84 - Toledo, OH - LSO File, 8 (Reel 59)
  - Local 84 - Toledo, OH - Proposition #2290 Kathy Campbell, 1988; 9 (Reel 59)
  - Local 86 - Reno, NV - Organizing Subsidy, 1988; 10 (Reel 59)
  - Local 88 - Toronto, Ontario, Canada - LSO's Two Plan Proposition #2173, 11 (Reel 59)